the only thing he did was publish it because
lo único que hizo fue publicarla porque
what Diego Arrabal did was publish it on his
lo que hizo diego arrabal área en sus
social networks, his Instagram, on his
redes sociales su instagram en su
Twitter, everything was public, on
twitter en todo fue pública en la
my car's license plate, okay, full
matrícula de mi coche vale full
Telecinco is full way of working,
telecinco es full manera trabajar de
full TV factory, okay, he came to
full fábrica de la tele vale llegó a
steal for the only thing that is not in the
robar por lo único que no está en la
TV factory because he ended up fighting
fábrica de la tele porque acabo peleado
with them with the issue of such and such, but Diego
con ellos con el tema de tal pero diego
Arrabal comes from where they come from
arrabal viene de dónde vienen
that is the way of Diego Arrabal that they
esa es la forma de diego arrabal que
have trying to threaten me to shut me up is
tienen intentar amenazar me callarme es
how you are criticizing me, take public,
como me estás criticando toma público
public for everything, understand your
público por todo entiende tus
register us so that everyone has
matricularnos para que todo mundo tenga
your data, I
tus datos
already told you, I could disqualify him but you
ya os dije podría descalificarlo pero os
have rated yourself and
habéis calificado el solo y
the rabble who was defending him, you
la gentuza que estaba defendiendo lo
are scum, I am, I am scum,
sois escoria soy soy escoria de verdad
you can really leave here and take it up the ass
os podéis ir de aquí y lo tomar por culo